PAJARI RODSAWANG

UX/UI DESIGNER

Mobile: 0474659918 Email PajariR@outlook.com www.pajari.myportfolio.com Melbourne. Australia

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Creative and empathetic UX designer who loves generating new ideas from user research. Strengths in communication, organisation and data analysis. A quick learner who is dedicated to solving problems to bring a positive impact to the world.

SKILLS

Technical

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript

UX/UI

- User Research
- UI Grids and Composition
- Color Theory
- Heuristic Evaluation
- Interaction Design,
- Storyboarding
- Persona Creation

Tools

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Miro
- Google Drive
- Zoom Meeting
- Slack

PROJECT SAMPLE

Native ARC Website Redesign

https://pajari.myportfolio.com/uxui-case-study-web-redesign

- Conducted user research to understand the first impression of the original website.
- Synthesised data based on user research and prioritised main focuses of the redesign.
- Created wireframes and prototypes and conducted usability testing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Learning Concierge

E180 | 2018 - 2019

- Facilitated intentional networking opportunities at live events such as CEBIT Australia and Digital Innovation Festival.
- Assisted with application on-boarding process and helped patrons connect with their first network based on topics they were interested in.

Content Writer

Ranked.ai | 2017-2018

 Worked autonomously to translated digital marketing content from English to Thai.

EDUCATION HIGHLIGHTS

University of London

BCS Computer Science | 2020 - Present

- · Member, Student Voice Group
- Volunteer, Computer Science Social Night

Monash University

UX/UI Bootcamp Certificate | 2020 - Present

- User experience design
- · User interface design
- Front-end development